Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries
No living creature was harmed during
the filming of this series.
Episode 104
Alps!
Alps.
I came.
My Bey.
I'm here, brothers.
I came.
- My Bey.
- Cerkutay.
I caught you, brother.
I caught you.
- My brother.
- My Bey.
Thank Allah.
Hold up, hold up, hold up.
My Bey.
Come on brother, come on.
I'm fine, I'm fine, my Bey.
Hang on.
Alps.
Baysungur.
Boran.
My brother, my brother.
I caught you.
Hang on.
Are you okay?
My valiant.
Osman.
I would make you food for crows...
but this cave has become your tomb.
Olof.
We searched everywhere.
There is no other exit to this cave.
Saga.
I avenge you, my brother.
I was going to stick this
dagger into your heart, Osman...
but now I will leave it at your grave.
What will we do if the
enemy is leaderless?
We'll raid his country...
and we kill the scattered
soldiers with the sword...
and we attack his flocks...
and we make all the people slaves..
and we kill them all with an axe.
If the enemy does not have a
leader, they will scatter.
and the scattered enemy...
becomes our bait.
Osman's death will turn
Yenişehir upside down.
After this mess...
our storm will destroy Yenişehir...
...but first...
we'll make sure he's dead.
Let some men stay here.
If the impossible happens and
someone gets out of here...
let them kill them.
Osman is dead, Olof.
Why would we leave our men here?
We'll make sure he's dead.
In order not to overshadow our victory.
These guys are not for him...
but for the sake of whoever
comes to take him out.
Come on.
You both.
Wait here.
Sarıca.
Thank Allah.
Come on.
Hang on.
Make a sound, brother Boran.
Brother.
Boran.
Say something.
Come on, brother.
Brother.
Boran.
No, no, make a sound, Boran.
Make a sound, Boran.
My Allah, help us.
My Allah.
Grant us your mercy, my Allah.
Save my valiants.
Boran.
Brother, don't you hear?
Make a sound, Boran.
Make a sound, make a sound, brother.
Boran, Boran.
Brother, get up, get up, get up.
Get up, stay awake.
Thank Allah.
My Allah.
Pull yourself together.
- Hold on, brother.
- Boran.
Look at me, are you okay?
You are awake, right?
I'm good.
He's still alive, my brother.
Hold on, my brothers, hold on.
This will not kill us.
However...
what will revive us is determination.
Hang on.
This place is closed.
There must be some way out.
Yenişehir
Malhun Hatun.
Bala Hatun.
Is there news about Osman Bey?
No news, he was supposed to come by now.
The news that came at night.
Beware that they have used Konur
Alp to lure Osman Bey into a trap.
Prepare the warriors, we are
going to take Osman Bey.
There must be some way out.
Hang on.
Hang on, my dear Boran.
Sarıca.
- Baysungur.
- My Bey.
Brother Boran, are you okay?
Brother.
- Brother.
- Oh, brother.
Give me strength, my Allah.
Do your best.
Hang on, Osman.
We will not stay here.
We've gone through many things.
We overcame many difficulties.
I am not fighting a war that has
begun, but I am starting a war.
Whoever harms us will pay the
price for that many times over.
You will always be one body.
You support each other.
For Alps.
And for the sake of children.
And for a country that will live forever.
Do your best.
Konur.
Brother.
Hang on.
Come on, hang on, brother.
Come on.
Brother
Get up, come on.
You will be fine.
Konur, my brother.
You'll be fine, brother.
Come.
Come on, brother.
Come on, drink it.
You will be fine.
In the name of of Allah the Merciful.
O Allah.
Hang on, brother.
Hang on.
Brother.
You will be fine.
Hang on, Osman.
Hang on.
My Bey.
- We won't leave you alone.
- You're all right, aren't you?
Yenişehir
Look under every stone, Bala,
and find Osman Bey.
We'll find him, Malhun, we'll find
him, don't worry.
Be careful, those who play
games against Osman Bey will not stop.
- Enemies surround us on every side.
- Don't worry.
What if something bad
happened to my father?
what shall we do?
We'll do what Osman Bey
would do in a situation like this.
Sons, we are now in the most
difficult times and we will unite.
And we will be stronger than ever.
We will not despair.
We will cling to hope and protect
Osman Bey's trust as we should.
Aktemur, increase the number of Alps
in Yenişehir.
Put five warriors in the place where you put two of them, we will not allow the passage of the infidels.
And tell all Beys to come, and we
will quickly convene the court.
If Osman Bey is not here, his son is.
- Orhan Bey, Bey of Karacahisar.
- Yes, mother.
You will deputize for Osman Bey in
the court as the Bey of Karacahisar.
Do you agree with that, Bala Hatun?
Orhan Bey can fulfill this task properly.
I agree, Malhun Hatun.
And what do you think, Alaaddin Bey?
If Osman Bey was here, he would have
ordered it, Malhun mother.
The head of the Court is
my brother's right.
Your command is like Osman Bey's
command, mother.
So, Orhan Bey is the one
who will head the court.
And the system will run in Yenişehir
as if Osman Bey is completely there.
Come back with the good news, Bala.
- May Allah help us
- Amin.
I entrusted you to Allah! Come on, Alps.
Come on.
My Allah, be with them.
I have brought the
fabrics you requested.
But I think the time is not right.
No, you came just in time, Marta
Let the Alps pay you, but
you must go nowhere.
I mean, don't run
around, I'll pass you by.
You're late, Kantakuzenos.
I'm never late, Olof, speak up.
I buried Osman alive in the dirt.
He is now at the table of demons.
Now it's all Turks' turn.
Did he die? And how did that happen?
Osman came to save that dog named Sarkis.
I demolished a large
cave over their heads.
Olof, Osman has devilish tricks.
Even if Osman is the devil, he won't emerge
from under the rubble of those stones.
Do not worry! They died like rats inside.
Even their corpses could not be obtained.
And my men surround that cave.
Osman has found the end he deserves.
And now we'll get everything we deserve.
Yenişehir and Karacahisar and
all the lands that belong to us.
Osman's absence will cause a civil war.
And they can't stop it.
An army without a
leader will end in defeat, Olof.
And what about Ophelia?
What happened to her?
Her body is on its way to the Emperor.
She has wiped out like anyone who
stands against us, Kantakuzenos.
That's cool.
So let's shed some Turkish
blood and destroy Yenişehir.
Watch out, Orhan! They will test you.
They will test your strength.
Don't worry, mother! I have held many
councils with the masters of Karacahisar.
And I know how to
manage it.
There you are the master of a state, but
here you will sit at the head of the state.
Your father's shadow
overshadows their bravery there.
Those who are against Osman will try to
make you obey them.
They will show themselves as affected
by your father's absence.
They will appear concerned and
have good intentions but...
There will be those among them who
do not wish Osman Bey to come back.
There are many enemies but are
there any enemies in the court, mother?
Orhan, everyone is fighting to fill the
void when the center of power is absent.
Power makes everyone
compete for it, including the good people.
Don't ever worry, mother.
We will discipline these souls
that struggle for power.
May Allah protect us from falling
into the whims of power.
Our job is to spread justice.
We are on standby.
Even if they oppose me, I will
oppose them all.
Inshallah, my son.
You look so well, and being the head of
the Court will also look good on you.
Inshallah, my mother!
Amin.
If we are going to establish
a state, it is thanks to the mothers.
May Allah bless you.
My Bey.
Kumral Abdal.
We are here.
Sir, the other exit to the mine is safe.
- We have to hurry.
- Yes.
Osman Bey.
Thank Allah.
Hey, hey!
My Bey.
Come on.
Thank Allah.
Thank Allah who brought us together.
Come on.
Blood.
There are traces of blood.
Alps, take precautions.
This way.
Come on.
My Osman.
Hang on.
Hang on, my brothers.
Brothers, are you all right?
Collect firewood.
Set fires.
No, no.
We can't light fires, they may
know where we are.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
My Bey.
Hang on.
Bite hard.
Thanks.
Alps.
- Bala.
- Osman.
Be careful, Alps.
My Osman.
My Bala.
You are fine, right?.
I'm fine, I'm fine
Alps? How are they, are they okay?
They are also fine.
Thank Allah we survived.
They will get better.
Bala.
We have to tell Malhun...
to increase the measures.
That dog, Olof...
His target will now be Yenişehir.
Before we came, Malhun appointed
Orhan as your agent.
Aktemur increased the number of Alps.
We have taken precautions beforehand.
Good, good what you did.
But it is not enough.
And now we're going to send her a letter.
They will protect the city
as if preparing for a big war.
Letter?
Why don't we go to them?
Shall we make the enemy rejoice, my Bey?
We will cheer them up
until they get drunk with joy.
My Bey, you say the enemy is at our gates.
Our children and our families.
Where are we going now
if we're not going to them?
To Marmaracık.
We're going to Marmaracık.
They went crazy in Osman's
palace a long time ago.
And his two wives are trying to
get back on their feet in his absence.
Malhun has taken over the reins.
As for Bala, she went to the cave.
To find the bones of her beloved husband.
Osman is dead.
And they will die too.
And the whole Yenişehir will be
affected by our black curse.
You'd better not speak
so confidently, Olof.
You know, Osman is a demon.
Not as much as us, Kantakuzenos.
If Osman had escaped from that cave...
would dear Malhun have been so troubled?
You have to learn to take
Frigg's word, Kantakuzenos.
Malhun panicked so much that she...
Orhan to replace Osman.
Poor Orhan, you should have
seen the fear in his eyes.
Nice.
That fear will bring them to their knees.
We will make this land on which our
blood has spilled a hell for them.
But we need more than this, Frigg.
You will know everything.
How many soldiers do they have?
How many archers?
You'll learn the number of
soldiers at each door.
I'll come up with more, my love.
I'll even know the breath in their lungs.
...but for now...
If you excuse me.
First Yenişehir.
And then we shall have the
Byzantine throne, Olof.
The army of Byzantium
will be under your command.
And your name will be remembered
with the brave warriors for ages.
First, let's hang Orhan's
head on Yenişehir.
Now the dog Olof knows I died in the cave.
He thinks I'm under the ground.
We'll take Marmaracık like never expected.
And since he thinks you're dead, he'll
take all his men to Yenişehir.
Exactly, it will leave Marmaracık empty.
We will take advantage of that void.
Now?
The Alps are wounded.
How are we going now?
Alps will go to the tribe.
Cerkutay.
My Bey.
Go with the Alps to the
tribe and treat them.
But secretly, don't let anyone see you.
Your command, my Bey.
Come on, my brothers, come on.
Since we're hunting Olof...
we should explore.
Let's go to Marmaracık, which
will belong to us.
Let's go, Osman Bey.
Come on.
Come on, Alps.
Yenişehir
Where is Osman Bey?
Has anyone seen it?
Alps came out all of a
sudden, that's what we heard.
Is it possible to leave this
position to a child of this age?
Beys.
Calm down.
And do not speak without knowledge.
And do not eat your brother's flesh.
They don't say anything, Öktem Bey.
They don't say anything.
However...
They want to know too.
But they don't know what
they're talking about.
Let them control their tongues.
So that we don't have to
teach them the limits.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Attention.
Go ahead.
With the ninety-nine
names of Allah, the court opens.
In the name of Allah the Merciful.
May I, Orhan Bey?
What happened, Orhan Bey?
Is it true what we heard?
What did you hear, Bayındır Bey?
How is Osman Bey?
I hope his health is fine.
Osman Bey is out to
solve a very important matter.
He left to me the Head of the Court as his representative, in my capacity as the Bey of Karacahisar.
Osman Bey went out to conquer many times.
He is a great Bey who does not say
what he does or what he thinks.
This is the first time we see that he
appointed his son in his absence.
It is clear that his return
this time is difficult.
You're thinking of Orhan Bey, aren't you?
I know he will do his job perfectly.
Those who want to take advantage of
Osman's absence will be taught the lesson.
It is our right to know as Beys...
We want to take our positions
according to the situation.
Isn't it, Beys?
Yes.
Bayındır Bey.
A Bey's business is secret.
I will share this secret with you.
But it's heavy.
Either I keep you in jail until
the campaign is over...
Or I have to chop off your heads.
Now tell me, Beys.
Do you still want to listen?
Yes, Orhan Bey.
- Well, Orhan Bey.
- He says it's a secret.
Don't you hear what our Bey says,
Demirhan Bey? He says it's a secret.
We must hear the Bey's words.
If your questions are over, I want to
hear about the other problems now.
Yenişehir
Osman Bey's Palace
We wanted to ask about Osman Bey
and he said lots of things.
That is what would happen if
the work was left to a young boy.
This is not good.
Beys.
Orhan Bey asked...
and you told him your problems...
and then the court ended.
What do you want next, Beys?
When did it become wrong to
ask about Osman Bey?
Didn't Orhan Bey' answer
convince you, Uraz Bey?
If you think so...
you will wait for Osman Bey in prison.
Isn't what you say shameful, Turgut Bey?
If you want to see the fault, look
at each other's faces.
No need to talk yet.
The Court is over.
Mind your business.
They're planning something again.
It will appear soon, whatever.
If you accept...
I want to share with you the business
that I am going to do in Marmaracık.
Thank you.
However...
While there are a lot of
dealers around, why me?
Because you are the most
skilled trader in this city.
And the richest, Bayındır Bey.
Aren't you in charge of everything here?
Yes...
Let's say I'm awake.
Don't be afraid.
For example, Osman Bey...
They say he's not around.
I'm sure no one else knows
the truth about it.
Hatun.
You are overrating me.
I only know what everyone else knows.
Orhan sits on the chair
in place of Osman Bey.
And Alps are on guard everywhere.
May Allah forbid.
I hope nothing bad happened to Osman Bey.
No, I hope you're wrong.
I don't even want to
think about Osman Bey's death.
No.
I do not want that.
Who wants?
May Allah keep Osman Bey above our heads.
However...
This is what it looks like, what
can we say?
I pray to Allah to grant Orhan Bey
strength and power, Inshallah.
While the surroundings are
complicated...
the best we can do is trade, Bayındır Bey.
It is not clear what
will happen to the city.
We must increase our profits.
Let's increase it.
But let's talk about terms first.
The goods your responsibility.
Finding clients is my responsibility.
And our profits will be equal.
I want two-thirds.
This is not the time to bargain.
I accept, we agreed.
Wait for word from me, Bayındır Bey.
Good.
Show up.
Tell me, what is the
situation in Marmaracık?
They got most of the soldiers out, my Bey.
The castle is available for attack.
But things are never good, my Bey.
They captured our brother Torahan.
Dogs.
They will all get their punishment.
I will cut their flesh off their bodies.
They got those soldiers out
to attack Yenişehir.
And we will take Marmaracık.
And we will save Torahan.
Wherever we had to spy, we
made that place home, my Bey.
What is our job in conquest?
First, you will close the horse stables.
They can't escape anywhere.
And when we go inside, you
will kill the archers on the walls.
When we pull our bows,
we will not leave any of them alive.
May Allah bless you.
Now go to your work.
But know the place of
the prison very well.
We'll take Torahan first.
We've known him
for a while, my Bey.
It's a map of the castle.
Oh my!
May Allah bless my valiants.
Come on, then.
May our conquest be blessed.
Thank you, my Bey.
Where are we going
now, my dear Osman?
To the place where it all began.
To our tribe.
Come on.
The trade of Marmaracık will benefit
you and our city, Bayındır Bey.
We allow you.
This is the permission document.
We don't ask for one thing for ourselves.
All our money and possessions are
sacrificed for the sake of Osman Bey.
This trade will please you, Malhun Hatun.
Inshallah, Bayındır Bey.
Come on, Allah bless you.
Take care.
My Bey.
Do you hear the sound
of gold coins, Hüseyin?
How can I not hear, my Bey_
Did you know anything
about Osman Bey?
It is said that Osman Bey
went out at night.
And he never came back again.
Osman is not around.
And Orhan holds the court
Obviously, they know something, however...
They hide it from us.
Something crosses my mind, however...
What if he is dead, my Bey?
Don't say that.
I worked so hard to get him to like me.
All my efforts are in vain.
You know...
Maybe his absence makes
us win a lot of coins, right?
Come on, you go.
And write a letter to Sencer Bey
telling him everything that happened.
Your command, my Bey.
Then prepare Marta's goods.
We'll set off early tomorrow morning.
Your command.
Of course, come on.
So, you don't feel anything
for me, do you?
So, say this to my face.
Subasi
Alçiçek.
Do you want something?
We'll talk.
There is nothing to talk about.
Get away from my table.
I said we'll talk, Alçiçek Hatun.
Alone
Shall I not get rid of you, Subasi?
What are you seeking, Subasi?
Say what you're going to say.
I don't have much time.
I'll ask a question and go.
I heard some things last night.
But my ears and heart can't believe it.
What you heard is true, Subasi.
So, say it again as you
look me in the eye.
Heads up, Alçiçek.
Do you want your heart broken, Subasi?
Does it matter for you?
Alçiçek.
I loved you.
Do you love me too?
No.
You misunderstood me, Subasi.
If I am the reason for this...
sorry.
Take these too.
If my mother had not come...
I wouldn't have taken it.
I bought these two earrings for you.
If they don't matter to you....
throw them away.
I...
I was wrong.
Excuse me.
I won't bother you again and I
won't get in your way.
Take your dagger, too.
Never hurt anyone again.
Aktemur.
You loved the wrong person, however...
you got the answer.
Don't, Alçiçek.
Don't.
Hurr up, Bayındır.
Otherwise, Osman's
nephew will not calm down.
Our tent, which was the
home of our big dreams...
Bala.
Thank Allah.
It was our privilege to see
those dreams come true, my Bey.
We have planted the seeds
of state in this tribe.
May Allah make you among
His righteous servants.
Amin.
In the name of Allah the Merciful.
You are the ones who will
carry the banner of Allah.
Move your horses forward.
Now, we take care of the it and
make it grow in Yenişehir.
I pray to Allah that He swears for us to
see it as a tree and harvest its fruits.
Amin, my dear Osman.
On the one hand, they
considered you invaders.
On the other hand, you rest,
Do not be jealous of
your brothers, Cerkutay.
Turgut Bey.
I've done all of that work.
And no one came and
called me Ghazi Cerkutay.
Brother.
Didn't you rest all this time because
you weren't hearing?
Yes.
I did.
I ate and drank a lot.
You will not like the
food of the tribe anymore.
You're used to
Ülgen Hatun's food, aren't you?
Now...
In fact, she is a skilled woman.
Cerguday.
It's like she's taking revenge
on me for the times I didn't hear.
I can hear her voice even
though she's not here.
Oh.
Really, Cerkutay?
Do you hear Ülgen Hatun's voice now?
Cerguday, come on!
Do you still hear it?
I hear it.
She is calling me
Please, brother, do not fear us.
Cerkutay.
You're basically a Ghazi.
And it didn't stop
at hearing the voice.
I smell.
I smell her food.
The smell of bulghur.
My Allah.
Don't worry, my dear Cerkutay.
We also hear Ülgen Hatun's voice.
But smelling that food is only your skill.
Are you deceiving me?
Allah forgive you.
Come on, run, don't make the bulghur wai.t
Come on.
Go eat your food.
Eat it all.
Cerguday.
Thank you, I was very hungry, Ülgen Hatun.
But I still don't hear.
What? How?
Do not you hear?
I came on foot.
He doesn't hear.
Anyway.
Eat, Cerguday, eat.
Enjoy it.
Don't worry, don't worry, I'll find
a way to heal your ears.
They said there was a herb.
There is a herb.
Enjoy it.
I found it.
Did you understand? I will
find it and heal your ears.
What am I doing?
You eat, Cerguday, eat bread too.
The food is very tasty.
- Enjoy it.
- Thank you.
What do you say? I do not hear you!
I don't hear, I don't hear!
Right?
Good.
Ülgen Hatun.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving, eat your food.
In the name of Allah.
Thank you, may Allah bless
your hands, Ülgen Hatun.
Enjoy it.
Enjoy it, brother.
I hope you'll leave us food.
Come, brother, there is
enough food for all of us.
I no longer hear.
I do not hear.
Cerguday will leave for us, right?
Osman Bey summons you.
We must not keep my Bey waiting.
Marmaracık Castle)
Yenişehir
It is smashed by our enemies.
But tomorrow, it will all
be over for the Turks.
We will take back our lands.
Explain, Frigg.
They are increasing the security
in Yenişehir, they are very worried.
Some soldiers came out.
They're obviously looking for Osman.
Let them search.
It will be difficult for them to find him
Continue, Frigg.
The largest door is the west door and
most units will be there.
And I'll clean that door
for Olof and his men.
The number of soldiers is not
enough to eliminate these units, my love.
For this reason, I will have my
men sneak into the castle all day.
They will be there for
you to clean the door.
But I will make the main
attack from the east.
When their soldiers head west...
I will enter through the eastern door...
and I will crush all who come before me.
You will crush them, my love.
I'll scatter the men
who snuck in all over town.
And when the massacre
begins in the city...
The eastern door will
open completely for you.
They still think I'm their friend.
For this reason, I will take on
the most important mission.
I will enter the mansion with 20 soldiers.
You'll have entered the city while
they get busy with me.
And I'll be in front of Osman's family
when they find out about the massacre.
First, I will tell them to their faces
that the war has begun...
...then I will cut their throats.
And I will take care of the women
in the mansion.
I will cut off their gentle hands
that prepare delicious meals.
I will turn that mansion into a barn for
our beautiful horses.
But first, in order to make it defenseless,
I have to drag Malhun into my trap.
I will handle her outside.
Tomorrow, before sunset,
Yenisehir will be ours.
Only Yenisehir?
No.
The Turks killed the Cardinal.
So Vatican will give me a huge army.
I will take the emperor's throne first.
And then I will take back
our lands from the Turks
The army will be yours, Olof..
And that's why I'm here.
I will let my ravens eat all the Turks!
I will bring death to them all.
Yenisehir will be ours.
Ours.
It will be ours.
We'll conquer Marmaracik.
We will be quick and ruthless.
There mustn't even be a single mistake.
We'll go in and take it.
That place is now more than
just a property to us.
Turahan is imprisoned there.
We'll get him out of there safe and sound.
With his goods, inshallah.
Here it is.
The dungeon that Samil told us about.
Just below the castle hall.
While we eliminate the soldiers, a team
of Alps will enter the dungeon.
We will not waste time.
My Bey.
The siege of the castle can last for days.
Can we come in, my Bey?
Come!
Peace be upon you.
And may peace be upon you.
What do you do here?
My Bey, don't keep us away from the fight.
My Bey, a Ghazi's wound
is healed in another fight.
We will come too.
Fair enough.
However, conquering the castle
will not last for days.
We will ruin their homes and take them
without any alp being harmed.
Now, they will want to sneak into Yenişehir
while we're away.
First, they will attack and
they will be successful.
But it would never occur to them
that we would take Marmaracik.
The enemy is on alert.
We are not going to sleep tonight, sons!
Are the streets under control, Subasi?
I put an Alp on every street in Yenisehir.
Insufficient.
We don't know the
men power of the enemy.
Put three alps instead of one.
Mother, this is our home.
We should outnumber them.
I know, son.
I know, but Yenisehir is entrusted to us.
We cannot feel safe
just because its our land.
I will send messengers to Karacahisar.
My alps will be here in the morning.
I have placed archers on the roofs and
we have alps in each building...
...as they may attack at anytime.
This is not enough.
If we can't handle them outside,
we will draw back to our buildings.
Our narrow alleys will absorb their
advantage in number.
If necessary, we will withdraw
to the mansion.
We will destroy them one by one.
Kutlu Alp, tell the alps and dervishes.
No one will insist on fighting.
If necessary, they will retreat and
withdraw to the mansion.
Yes my Bey.
Send messengers to Inegol, Karacahisar,
Bilecik. Ask for reinforcement.
As you command, Malhun Hatun.
Yenisehir is entrusted to us.
We will take care of it, my Bey.
However...
The owner of this...
How are you now, Osman Bey?
I moved the alps from
Inegol to Yenisehir.
Yet I don't know if our forces
are sufficient, Osman Bey.
We will take our strength from the tribe.
We will attack with the alps in the tribe.
Will they be sufficient
for a siege, my Bey?
There is not going to be a siege.
The fortress will ask for provisions
from Bayindir Bey.
Malhun Hatun approved him.
We'll escort those three carriages.
They will be waiting for provisions.
When they open the gates
they will see us in front of them.
What about the security
of Yenisehir, my Bey?
Malhun Hatun will handle it.
Alps and dervishes will be in disguise
and guard the town.
But they will not stop them from
entering Yenisehir.
They will proceed to the center.
Olof and those with him
will march towards our trap.
We will attack them when the time comes.
First Marmarcik.
And then the whole world.
Oktem Tribe
Thank you.
Enjoy it.
Thank you, daughter.
Our Bey let the child sit on the throne
and who knows what adventure he's into!
Orhan Bey said what he had to say.
What are you questioning here, Bayindir?
What am I questioning here?
Whenever this man disappears from sight,
he comes back with a thousand troubles!
Who knows what kind of
trouble he'll cause now!
The last time he went to Constantinople...
...Batur Alp...
Bayindir!
Why do you keep bringing up
what's already over?
What is already over, Oktem Bey?
Bayindir Bey is right.
Hatun, even if it is still not over yet...
Osman Bey will give us the opportunity
to take revenge.
Marmaragic is about to be conquered.
It's that dog Olof's home!
I trust him completely.
Osman Bey will conquer Marmaracik.
And he will make it a home for the Turks!
We are not asking you not to trust.
We only ask you to be on alert.
Imagine what a man, who deceives
even the emperor, would do to you!
Don't you agree with me, Bengi Hatun?
It doesn't matter, Bayindir Bey.
Oktem Bey has become arrogant.
He trusts Osman Bey more than
he trusts you and me.
Stop this.
We trusted Osman Bey at the door of death.
He protected us at that time.
Don't worry about me.
Why are you angry, Oktem Bey?
If that man trusts you so much...
Why does he not disclose his location?
Why is he hiding it from you?
It's no use to trust someone
if they don't trust you back!
Time will show...
If I'm right about trusting Osman Bey,
or wrong like you say.
Good night, Bayindir.
Subasi is around Alcicek again.
Be careful.
Good night.
What is he saying, Bengi Hatun?
Nothing important,
it was about the stalls.
Good
Oh Alcicek!
I know what I will do to you.
Aktemur, son of Gunduz Bey,
who terrorized seven countries.
I shudder as I look into your eyes.
- I will make him talk!
- Alcicek!
You need to control your anger, Alcicek?
Are you well?
If I had a thousand necks, I'd sacrifice them
all to stop the tears dropping off your eyes.
If only that dagger had stabbed my heart
so I wouldn't have heard all these!
Alcicek Hatun.
This is enough.
Aktemur?
Come in, mother.
I fed my little boy Aydogdu
and put him to sleep, how is my big son?
Tell me, Aktemur,
which mountain are you on top of this time?
I'm under the ground, mother.
Don't worry about me.
How can a mother not worry about her son?
Do you think motherhood ends
when the boys grow up?
The tears you shed inside you, my son,
burn my heart.
Your heart has no reason to hurt, mother.
Relieve.
Son.
I have no one but you and your brother.
That's why I got mad at that girl.
- If she hurts my son...
- It's over, mother!
It's over now!
Alcicek thing is over.
She doesn't love me.
It's over.
Don't worry.
I hope for your best, son.
For the best.
I stabbed him.
But I am the one whose heart hurts.
Love issues are too hard.
Are you in love?
If you fell in love,
then why did you reject the man?
To test him.
And what do you mean by that,
Alcicek Hatun?
What if his feelings are not true?
What if its just a whim?
I must know first.
Does he really love me?
He must make me believe his love first.
So that I set off on this difficult way
with him.
Alcicek!
I told you not to meet that man.
You're in my tent and
describe the love you have for him?
Mother, I'm...
Will you let people gossip
about our family?
I won't allow it, Alcicek.
You are not going to see even his shade.
It's enough, mother!
Enough, what do you want from me?
Why are you pressing me like that?
Why are you so angry?
What wrong did Subasi do?
Isn't it wrong to hover around
you without my permission?
But I will also hold him
accountable for this immoral act.
How shameless!
Despite all my words,
he's still chasing you!
Mother!
Let your ears hear
what your mouth says!
Watch your words!
What immoral act
have you seen from Aktemur?
Pull yourself together!
You disobey your mother for the man
you met recently.
- Mother...
- Shut it!
Alcicek, shut it.
You will never see that young man again.
If he encounters you on the way,
you will change your path.
Kayi's men!
We will enter into a difficult battle!
Even if we don't walk to the enemy...
They will keep coming towards us.
This is a fight between right and wrong.
My strong-hearted alps!
Now it is time to strike the home of enemy
like a steel flail!
Marmaracik is a place which...
...reaches to the land of the enemy
like a hammer.
If we claim that fortress...
Many more conquers
will be available for us!
Our horses are facing forward
Our faces are always facing west
Come on Alps!
It's time to conquer!
Tell me Subasi, what's the situation?
We have sent messengers to all our lands,
they are preparing alps.
And I brought the alps from
Karacahisar to Yenisehir.
They are all waiting for
your orders, Mother.
What are the conditions around?
Did you take precautions around the town?
Our spies are walking around dressed as
shepherds and merchants, Malhun Hatun.
Ayse.
Any news on Marta?
The woman is like an ant.
She doesn't rest.
She is always working.
We'll see if she is a hardworking ant...
Or a snake who is waiting to bite.
Soldiers!
Today we will smear Yenişehir with blood!
We will end Turks...
...who shed our blood!
Soldiers!
Odin's table is for warriors!
Deserve Valhalla!
We will not pity on...
...anyone who shed our blood...
...anyone who damaged Byzantine!
We will kill everyone who gets in our way!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
You will infiltrate into Yenisehir.
Remember!
The easiest way to eliminate the enemy...
...is to damage it inside.
Some of you will die on this way.
Remove fear from your hearts!
Deserve the table of Odin!
And when the signal comes to you...
You will start the war.
To spread the black curse!
Black curse! Black curse!
Bey, they are coming
Let them come, let them come.
- Boran.
- My Bey.
- Get ready.
- Yes my Bey.
Has the gold been discovered, Huseyin?
Impossible, my Bey.
Put your weapons
back in their sheaths!
We go to Marmaracik to trade
so that the Turkmens can get rich
What sin have I done?
Why do you cross my road?
Your sins are between you and Allah,
Bayindir Bey.
You are what we need.
What's it, Turgut Bey?
For the Good's sake.
Watch who is coming.
Osman Bey.
Bayindir Bey.
You will take us to Karacahisar.
I give you my money, my possessions,
and my soul, Osman Bey.
But what is your plan?
Marmaracik is going to be
Turks' from now on.
You used to say that you love to fight.
Now is the time.
You will come with us.
What a shame it would be not to join you
on a holy fight, Osman Bey! Eyvallah!
Eyvallah.
Yenişehir without Osman is like
a warrior without armor, Olof.
I am going to visit my friends now.
Orhan Bey.
On his little shoulders...
...Yenisehir's huge responsibility.
How misfortune for him.
Go, Kantakouzanos.
Our friendship with them...
...is our biggest weapon.
It'll be last time
they see my friendly face.
And the first time they'll see
my enemy face.
I will gouge out their eyes.
I will fill fire in them.
Neither Orhan nor Malhun.
None of them will breathe.
I will not let anyone breathe in Yenisehir.
At the end of the war...
I will have taken my revenge,
you will have taken the gift you deserve.
The crown of Byzantine!
They have nowhere to run.
We will avenge and I will wear that crown!
We will attack from all four sides.
Let's go.
Come on, let's get started.
We will smear Yenişehir
with the black curse!
Go!
Oktem Tribe.
There is no news from Osman Bey yet.
What does he hide again?
Allah knows what calamity he will cause us
But you know this is your fault.
That man does whatever he wants to you.
Then he gives a speech
about fight and war.
- And you believe...
- What should I have done, Hatun?
What could we do when we stood with him
Osman Bey is getting stronger day by day.
We will get stronger too.
You won't be strong and grow bigger
waiting here like this.
Look at Osman!
He secretly solves all his business
without even taking a single breath!
It is not a time to stay idle.
We are not going to
stay idle either, Hatun.
Is Osman making a deal with
the infidels secretly hiding from you?
What he did before troubled us.
Let's see to whom
he will bring trouble now.
I will travel to Yenisehir, go to the
mansion and see if Hatuns know anything.
Don't worry.
I'll know what's going on.
I'll act as if I'm looking for you.
Don't leave the tribe today.
- Hatun!
- Don't worry Oktem Bey.
I will find out.
There is no other way.
What's wrong with Alcicek?
Nothing.
I solved it, don't worry.
Open the gates.
Only you can enter.
Is this reasonable?
What do you mean by that?
Will I carry all these goods myself?
- Huseyin!
- My Bey!
I changed my mind.
We are leaving!
Merchant!
You have just arrived,
where are you going?
What does it mean that you don't
let my men in?
We need only you.
Soldiers!
Search the wagons!
Turn it upside down!
We don't receive free goods everyday.
It's a trap! Soldiers, attack!
You are not getting any goods!
Karacahisar is ours from now on!
Samil! Aykut!
O Right!
Come on alps!
Allah is the greatest!
Attack them!
Turgut!
Samil, come on!
Don't resist, commander!
Don't resist.
Protecting Karacahisar Castle
is my mission!
I will fight you
until my last breath!
Are you all right, Commander?
What are you doing here?
Go fight!
I spilled my blood!
And I will cut your man
to pieces in front of you, Osman!
Inform Olof with a pigeon at once!
Osman is here! Run!
They're holding Turahan
at the end of the corridor, my Bey.
We didn't come here in vain, brother.
Of course we will get him out.
Are you okay brothers?
We are fine, thank Allah.
We will save our brother and make this
fortress a graveyard for them!
Come on then!
Let's go!
I showed you respect when
you came to Constantinople.
But Olof was right, you are not a friend.
You are not a friend.
You are the greatest enemy!
And you, like the Emperor,
do not know who is friend and who is foe!
You cannot deceive me, Osman Bey,
I will kill you and bury you here
This is my land now!
I decide who gets buried!
Boran!
Take Commander to the prison.
- He has things to tell me.
- Eyvallah my Bey!
Your death must be close.
You lost so much blood.
You are my ticket.
And when I get out of here,
I'll feed my dogs with you!
Move!
When Kantakouzanos and Frigg open
the gates of Yenisehir, we will attack
You will not pity anyone
Whoever shows mercy will be killed by me
after the war!
If you come back with a clean axe,
I will paint it with your blood!
Have courage, brothers!
We will rip out the heart of Turks!
I don't want any mistakes!
Everyone who opposes us in this land...
...will be dead!
Freddy.
Come quickly, Olof!
Osman is not dead.
He has come with his men
and they are going to take the castle.
No!
no!
Osman! Osman!
I don't know how you got out of that hole!
But Marmaracik will be your grave.
Olof.
What do we do now?
No!
Tell Frig right away!
They have to raid Yenisehir without us.
Let's go!
We are going to Marmaracik at once!
And we'll walk around holding
Osman's head!
Come on! Come on!
Turahan, my brother.
This is not good.
Where is this Turahan, brother?
This way, Turgut Bey.
Let's go.
Boran!
I didn't give up on you under the rock.
Do you think I would now?
My Bala.
Thank Allah.
You will die.
You lasted too long.
Go ahead.
Stop talking and act.
That dog is here.
We are here brother.
We will not leave you with the infidel!
Step back!
Get out of here now, I'm out of here!
You can't go anywhere.
Even if you get out of here,
you can't control this lion.
Come on brother.
Are you fine?
I'm fine brother.
It was a nice fight.
If you didn't have me...
How would you cross
these great walls?
We would demolish and enter.
Yes, it's not something
we haven't done before.
We would destroy everything.
Yes.
So don't boast about yourself,
Bayindir Bey.
Bala Hatun.
Your alps underestimate my service!
Not at all, Bayindir Bey.
Thank you very much.
Your business has been very profitable.
Turks have another property now.
I would go up until Constantinople if
Osman Bey asked me to do so!
Thank you very much.
Bala Hatun is grateful to us.
We now know who we are going to approach
to get close with Osman Bey.
We know it now, my Bey.
Marmaracik is ours now.
Take down the flags!
Bala.
My Bey!
Thank you very much, my Allah.
Thank you very much.
Welcome Bengi Hatun.
Where's Malhun Hatun, Ulgen Hatun?
What's it, Bengi Hatun?
Yenişehir is empty.
I can't find the person I'm looking for.
Everyone is in their business
and occupations.
I'm looking for Oktem Bey,
but I can't find him
I heard that Osman Bey is absent as well.
Did they go somewhere together?
Do you know anything?
Bengi Hatun, I know what I should know.
I know where Osman Bey is.
However, it's not me who should know where
Oktem Bey is. It's you.
Do you think I know?
There are someone else who knows him
better than me!
Come in.
Here.
For you.
Thank you.
Oktem is reserved, Malhun Hatun.
But he is reserved only to me.
He doesn't tell me where
he's going or what he's doing.
He wasn't like this with Zuleyha.
He would consult her first,
he would go and tell her about it.
I don't understand, Bengi Hatun.
Who is Zuleyha?
The first wife of Oktem.
Zuleyha.
Look, I feel uncomfy even while
mentioning her name.
I didn't know he was married before.
Nobody knew it.
Same story, Malhun Hatun.
Zuleyha wasn't able to give birth.
She is dead and gone.
But...
Oktem's love for her never ended.
Every time I look inside Oktem's eyes,
I see Zuleyha.
But what can I do?
She is the first wife!
Don't think I'm bad now.
No, not at all.
The first wife is unforgettable.
You may think it's stupid to get jealous
of a dead person, but..
I'm jealous. That's it.
Women get jealous.
Aren't you jealous, Malhun Hatun?
Bengi Hatun, before everything,
we are a state.
We leave our feelings behind
when we deal with the state issues.
Jealousy is impotence.
We have no right to fall
into this heedlessness.
But you don't have such problems.
You don't know it.
So I am listening to you.
Tell me about it.
Thank you.
Not talking to anyone about this
makes me sick inside.
My heart could not bear it anymore,
so my tongue spoke it.
This issue isn't spoken with
a random person.
But you are not a random one.
You understand me.
I couldn't give Oktem a boy.
I had Batur, and he's gone too.
I only have Alcicek left in my tent now.
And I have no intention of ever losing her,
Malhun Hatun.
My daughter means everything to me.
A child is a mother's masterpiece,
Bengi Hatun.
Hug your daughter.
Digging down a ended issue
doesn't give you any good.
On the contrary, it damages you.
Don't think about it anymore.
It only hurts your heart.
Let me leave now.
I need to find my daughter
and my husband.
Of course, Bengi Hatun.
I have dropped the seeds of suspicion
inside you, Malhun Hatun.
You brave soldiers!
You are here to stain Yenisehir with blood
Listen to me very well now.
When Kantakouzanos gets into action...
We will attack the soldiers in the east
and open Olof's path.
You, Commanders.
You'll spread your soldiers all over
the city when Olof comes.
However....
...Keep your eyes on the mansion.
If even one person gets out, kill them.
We tracked everyone down
like you asked, ma'am.
Prince Aladdin is in the courthouse
and the others are in the mansion.
I will drink their blood.
How long do we have to wait,
Subasi Aktemur Bey?
.We'll let you in...
Whenever Malhun Hatun approves,
Kantakuzenos.
Impatience is not good, don't question.
Subasi, Malhun Hatun
is waiting for Kantakuzenos.
Here you go, Kantakuzenos.
I will stain my sword with your blood first
when Olof takes this city, Subasi.
You will live the same destiny
with your father.
Surround the shop!
Break the door!
Ayse Hatun.
What is going on like this?
Why do you lock your door
during the day, Hatun?
I'm scared.
Explosions.
There is constantly an incident in the town.
I locked my door.
Search, search everywhere.
There is nothing up there, Ayse Hatun.
Won't you say something?
What are you looking for?
There's a traitor, Marta.
We're looking for a trace.
Keep your eyes and ears open too, okay?
Alps, let's get out!
Their eyes are on us, act accordingly.
Malhun Hatun.
The best guests are the ones who
tell they're coming, Kantakouzanos.
Please, come.
Has Osman Bey not come yet?
Look, I brought gifts.
He didn't come.
But we got news from him.
What do you mean?
Osman Bey is in Marmaracik,
where now belongs to him.
I do not understand.
Let me explain further.
The property of Marmaragcik
belongs to Osman Bey from now on
He took it from our enemy Olof.
Why are you so surprised, Kantakouzanos?
You must rejoice.
Brother!
Are you okay brother?
I'm fine my Bey.
Oh brother!
Praise be to Allah
who brought us together
Here is my brother!
Don't worry, brother.
We are wounded too.
Turgut Bey.
May Allah bless you.
Eyvallah.
Reymos.
All the trouble came from
those dogs.
Listen carefully.
This will be the last you hear from them.
Tell me now!
So that I cut your head
at once!
Which one?
Do you want to hear how
we raided the town?
How we killed your men?
How we killed Batur?
Or how we put the whole blame on you?
This will be your last war Osman.
You will always attack.
But we will be the ones beating you.
You say this is the last war, right?
This is a war between right and wrong.
It will go on forever.
But you won't be able to see it.
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest
Remus is a good commander.
And he knows all the truth.
And he knows the tricks
that Olof pulls.
Take him to prison now.
He has something to tell me.
My Bey,
Olof and the rest are about to arrive.
Their number is large.
Come now.
Close the gates!
Archers, to the top!
Come on.
Come to us.
Come on brothers!
Pull, come on!
You will die, Osman!
Archers!
The infidels attack with full force!
They are a single body!
The Islamic world cannot unite.
Mongols at one hand.
Crusaders on the other hand.
They are on the offensive side.
We are on the defensive side.
This is difficult to accept.
How can we eliminate this crisis,
Sheikh?
Prophet says...
....Allah is hardworking.
And He loves the hardworkers.
The universe is in motion.
Rivers become a waterfall.
Day becomes night,
and night becomes day
Seasons change.
The moon is going away.
And the sun shines.
Therefore...
God loves movement and action.
He loves the rebirth.
For this reason, Muslims must be alive.
And they must always be working.
Work is important, my dears.
It is, my friends.
It very is.
The Islamic world
has forgotten working.
We must kindle the flame of jihad
in our heart again.
So, are we going to make
the oppressors obey us?
With Allah's permission, yes.
What else should we do, my sheikh?
Surah At-Tawbah answers your question.
"O believers! What is the matter with you
that when you are asked to march forth...
...in the cause of Allah,
you cling firmly to the land?"
(Surah At-Tawbah 38)
This means our unity is broken.
What does Allah suggest us,
Prince Aladdin?
Allah Almighty says in Surah At-Tawbah...
"if you do not march forth, He will afflict you with
a painful torment and replace you with other people.
You are not harming Him in the least.
And Allah is Most Capable of everything."
(Surah At-Tawbah 39)
Who are the ones Allah loves, Prince Orhan?
Allah Almighty says in Surat Al-Saff...
"Surely Allah loves those who fight in His cause in
solid ranks as if they were one concrete structure."
(Surah As-Saf 4)
Praise e!
Praise be to you!
I don't need to lecture you!
You have all the answers!
For this reason,
we will get rid of laziness and work.
In the name of Allah the Merciful,
the Compassionate.
My Allah, do not put pressure on your
valiants who fight in your cause.
And they attack the enemy
when the morning comes.
Help them.
- Amen.
Do not let our valiants
be humiliated in front of the infidels.
- Amen.
Grant us victory over the infidels.
Let the Islamic world unite
against the infidels again.
Amen.
Make the Islamic world gain its glory again.
Let them become brothers, and unite.
- Amen.
May they become one body and be strong.
Amen.
I'll swing your head on these walls!
You are only talking!
But I perform!
No!
The time for talking is over!
From now on, only the voice
of crying will be heard!
Osman!
Shout as long as you want!
Marmaracik Castle became
the property of the Turks
Allah is the greatest!
Allah is the greatest
Please contact turkision@gmail.com for any inquiries